const STORE = [
    {
      question: 'This treaty saw the abdication of Kaiser Wilhelm I and the downsizing of the German army following their defeat in World War I.',
      answers: [
        'Treaty of Prussia',
        'Treaty of Versailles',
        'Treaty of Bruges',
        'Treaty of Weimar'
      ],
      correctAnswer:
        'Treaty of Versailles'
    },
    {
      question:
        'This was the name of the provisional government set up by the Allies following the German defeat in World War I.',
      answers: [
        'Weimar Republic',
        'Prussian Republic',
        'Wilhelm Republic',
        'Versailles Republic'
      ],
      correctAnswer:
        'Weimar Republic'
    },
    {
      question:
        'This country was the birthplace of Adolf Hitler.',
      answers: [
        'Germany',
        'Poland',
        'Austria',
        'Hungary'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Austria'
    },
    {
      question: 'During his imprisonment, Adolf Hitler wrote this manifesto which would hold all of his core politics and ideologies.',
      answers: [
        'Sturm und Drang',
        'Der Frieschutz',
        'Mein Kampf',
        'Liebe-Hutten'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Mein Kampf'
    },
    {
      question:
        'In his rise to power Hitler had a strong hatred for this ethnic group and blamed all of Germany’s current problems on them.',
      answers: [
        'Gentiles',
        'Jews',
        'Muslims',
        'Aryans'
      ],
      correctAnswer:
        'Jews'
    },
    {
      question: 'This was the name of the German Secret police set up by the Third Reich to weed out enemies of the state.',
      answers: [
        'Gestapo',
        'FAMAS',
        'Purgis',
        'FARC'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Gestapo'
    },
    {
      question:
        'This word in German means "Lightning War" and it was also the name for the German’s attack on London.',
      answers: [
        'Schadenfreude',
        'Blitzkrieg',
        'Eisenreich',
        'Panzer'
      ],
      correctAnswer:
        'Blitzkrieg'
    },
    {
      question: 'This was the name of the German Air Force under the command of Herman Goring which was instrumental during the attack on London.',
      answers: [
        'Schnieder',
        'Panzer',
        'Luftwaffe',
        'Wehrmacht'
      ],
      correctAnswer:
        'Luftwaffe'
    },
    {
      question: 'During Operation Barbarossa, this major Russian city was the main target and the site of the Nazi’s defeat in the Soviet Union.',
      answers: [
        'Moscow',
        'Leningrad',
        'Stalingrad',
        'St. Petersburg'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Stalingrad'
    },
    {
      question:
        'This man was the leader of the infamous Afrikaan Panzer Corps whose shrewd tactics with tanks earned him the alias Desert Fox.',
      answers: [
        'Herman Goring',
        'Rudolph Hess',
        'Erwin Rommel',
        'Heinrich Himmler'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Erwin Rommel'
    }
  ];